FORTY-LOVE!
四十了 親愛的!
THIS IS MATCH POINT. YOU READY?
賽點到了 准備好了么?
FINALLY. LET'S GET IT OVER WITH.
決勝球 我們來分個高下吧
ACE!
發球得分!
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT GOING EASY ON ME
我希望你不是在對我放水
'CAUSE I'M NEW AROUND HERE.
因為我新搬來這邊
EASY? WHAT, THAT WAS BRUTAL!
放水?我開玩笑 我可是毫不留情的!
MY SWEAT HAS SWEAT.
我已經汗流浹背了
WHAT, ARE YOU SOME KIND OF TENNIS HUSTLER OR SOMETHING?
難道你是個網球騙子還是其他什么么?
FIGURE NEW TOWN, NEW SCHOOL,
算計著去新的小鎮 新的學校
NEW UNEXPECTING KIDS TO BEAT?
打敗某個沒有准備的孩子?
HEY, I DIDN'T TAKE YOUR MONEY OR ANYTHING.
嘿 我可沒拿走你的錢或者其他東西
NO, JUST MY SELF RESPECT.
是的 除了我的自尊心
LOOK OUT!
小心!
DIANA, I TOLD YOU, FOLLOW THROUGH.
Diana 我告訴過你 隨球動作
IT'S ALL ABOUT THE FOLLOW THROUGH. COME ON.
所有都是隨球動作 接著來
ANY DAY NOW.
給我呀你
YOU'RE WELCOME.
不客氣
Ned: WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
怎么回事?
YOU KNOW DIANA MORRISON?
你認識Diana Morrison?
I USED TO, BACK WHEN I LIVED IN GRANDVIEW THE FIRST TIME.
曾經是的 還在我第一次住在Grandview的時候
WE WERE FRIENDS. DIANA?
我們曾經是朋友 Diana?
OH, MY GOD, WHAT HAPPENED?
哦 我的天 發生了什么事?
IT WAS LIKE A MILLION YEARS AGO. DIANA?!
- 好像都是几百年前的事情了 - Diana?!
DIANA? OH, MY GOD, WHAT HAPPENED?! DIANA, DIANA! SOMEBODY HELP!
Diana? 哦 上帝啊 怎么了 Diana Diana!來個人幫幫忙!
DIANA! DIANA, PLEASE!
Diana! Diana 醒醒!
DIANA, DIANA! PLEASE WAKE UP!
DIana  Diana!快醒醒!
WHAT HAPPENED?
怎么了?
SHE JUST DROPPED OUT OF NOWHERE,
她忽然失去知覺倒下了
SHE WON'T RESPOND! I'M CALLING 9-1-1.
- 她沒有反應! - 我打9-1-1
I'LL STAY HERE. GO GET HELP.
我呆在這里 快去找人幫忙
DIANA, IT'S OLIVIA. Coach: OK.
-Diana 我是Olivia - 好的
DIANA, PLEASE WAKE UP! YES, WE NEED AN AMBULANCE.
- Diana 快醒醒啊! - 是的 我們需要一輛救護車
GRANDVIEW PARK AT THE TENNIS COURTS. A GIRL'S COLLAPSED.
Grandview公園的網球場 有個女孩子昏倒了
DIANA! DIANA! WAKE UP!
Diana! Diana!醒醒!
WAKE UP! DIANA! DIANA, PLEASE.
醒醒! Diana!Diana 求你了
DIANA, WAKE UP!
Diana 醒過來啊!
WHY WON'T YOU WAKE UP? WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
為什么你不醒過來?你到底怎么了?
DIANA... DIANA!
Diana... Diana!
THANK YOU. SURE.
- 謝謝 - 不客氣
THANK YOU, NURSE.
謝謝你 護士
JIM. HI, DOCTOR.
Jim 你好 醫生
MELINDA, HOW YOU FEELING? I FEEL OK.
- Melinda 你感覺如何? - 很好
NO MORE NAUSEA, LIGHT-HEADEDNESS?
沒有惡心和輕微頭疼了?
UM, NO.
呃 沒有
WELL...
嗯...
YOU'RE NOT PREGNANT.
你沒有懷孕
YEAH, WE- WE FIGURED AS MUCH.
是的 我們 我們也猜到了
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT THE PREGNANCY TEST SAID, TOO.
是的 妊娠測試也是這么說的
ALL TEN OF THEM.
全部指數都是10
SO THEN...
所以說...
EVERYTHING THAT I WAS FEELING...
我感覺到的一切...
IT WAS ALL JUST IN MY HEAD?
都只是我自己的想象而已?
NO, YOU DID CONCEIVE,
不 你的確有懷孕的跡象
BUT YOUR BODY DIDN'T SUPPORT THE PREGNANCY.
但是你的身體卻沒有支持這一點
DOC, WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
醫生 這是什么意思?
IF YOU'RE WORRYING ABOUT YOUR CHANCES OF HAVING A BABY, DON'T.
如果你是在擔心受孕的几率 那么完全不必顧慮
THERE'S PLENTY OF TREATABLE CONDITIONS THAT CAN ACCOUNT FOR THIS.
對于這種情況我們有很多方法來解決
LET ME RUN SOME TESTS, AND WE'LL GO FROM THERE, OK?
我們來做一些測試 然后再從長計議 如何?
OK.
好的
THE NURSE WILL SCHEDULE YOUR NEXT APPOINTMENT.
護士會安排你的下一次預約時間
THANKS.
謝謝
HEY, HEY, HEY. WOW.
- 嘿 嘿 嘿 - 哇嗚
I NEVER REALLY FIGURED IT WOULD BE THIS HARD.
我從沒想過會如此難過
IT'S GONNA BE OK.
會雨過天晴的
WE'RE GONNA MAKE THIS HAPPEN, TOGETHER.
我們會一起努力渡過的
YOU NEED TO FINISH YOUR SHIFT.
你得輪完你的班
GO, I'LL BE OK.
去吧 我沒事
YOU SURE?
你確定?
YEAH.
嗯
'CAUSE YOU CAN HOLD ON TO MY HAND AS LONG AS YOU WANT.
你可以一直握著我的手 多久都可以
OH! SORRY.
哦!對不起
I LOVE YOU. I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
我愛你 等會見
DOC, BP 75 OVER 42. COMING IN!
- 醫生 血壓75/高于42 - 快進來!
PULSE IS RAPID AND IRREGULAR.
脈搏過快且紊亂
I WANT AN ECG AND A CHEST X-RAY.
我要一個心電圖和胸腔X光
AND GET ME A CONSENT TO TREAT.
給我一份治療許可
DO WE HAVE HER NAME? I'M ON IT!
- 知道她名字嗎? - 好的
DIANA MORRISON.
Diana Morrison
DOROTHY?
Dorothy?
NED, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
Ned 你在這干嘛?
ARE YOU OK? YEAH.
- 你還好么? - 還好
YEAH, I'M FINE. WE'RE BOTH FINE.
是的 我很好 我們都沒事
Doctor: ONE, TWO...
一 二...
GIRL COLLAPSED ON THE TENNIS COURTS.
有個女孩子在網球場昏倒
OLIVIA AND I WANTED TO MAKE SURE SHE WAS OK.
Olivia和我想確認她有沒有事
SHE HAS TO BE OK. OLIVIA!
- 她肯定沒事 - Olivia!
MOM!
媽媽!
I WENT TO THE COURTS TO PICK YOU UP
我到網球場接你
BUT YOU WEREN'T THERE,
可你不在
AND THEY SAID A GIRL HAD COLLAPSED! I THOUGHT THAT-
他們說有個女孩子昏倒了!我還以為
I'M FINE, MOM. I'M SORRY FOR SCARING YOU.
我很好 媽媽 對不起讓你擔心了
I SHOULD HAVE CALLED.
我應該打個電話給你
IT'S DIANA.
是Diana
DIANA MORRISON?
Diana Morrison?
WHERE'S DIANA MORRISON?
Diana Morrison在哪?
I'M HER MOTHER. THEY TOLD ME SHE WAS HERE.
我是她媽媽 他們告訴我她在這
OLIVIA?
Olivia?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
你在這做什么?
MRS. MORRISON, I WAS AT THE COURTS WITH NED.
Morrison太太 我和Ned在網球場
DIANA WAS THERE, TOO.
Diana也在那
SHE WAS TAKING A LESSON, I GUESS.
我想她正在上網球課
SHE JUST COLLAPSED.
然后她忽然倒下了
WAS IT HEAT STROKE?
是中暑么?
SHE MUST HAVE JUST FAINTED.
她肯定只是昏倒而已
SHE BARELY ATE ANY BREAKFAST.
她基本不吃早飯
Diana: NO!
不!
TIME OF DEATH...
死亡時間...
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, TIME OF DEATH?!
什么意思 死亡時間?!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
你還好吧?
DID YOU KNOW THIS GIRL?
你認識這個女孩?
NO, NO, I'M FINE.
不 不 我沒事
UM, TIME OF DEATH, 3:49.
呃 死亡時間 3:49
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?!
到底發生了什么?!
DO YOU KNOW ME?
你認識我嗎?
WAIT!
等等!
Mrs. Morrison: HOW IS DIANA?
Diana怎么樣了
WHEN CAN I SEE HER?
我什么時候可以看她?
ANSWER ME!
回答我!
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?!
到底發生了什么?!
ARE YOU THE DOCTOR?
您是醫生么?
WHEN CAN I SEE HER?
我什么時候可以看她?
YOUR DAUGHTER SUFFERED A BLOOD CLOT IN HER LUNG.
您女兒的肺部發生血液凝結
I'M VERY SORRY. WE DID EVERYTHING WE COULD,
很抱歉 我們已經盡力了
BUT WE WEREN'T ABLE TO REVIVE YOUR DAUGHTER,
可是還是沒辦法救回您女兒
AND SHE DIED. NO, NO!
- 她過世了 - 不 不!
NOT DIANA!
不可能是Diana!
NO! NOT MY LITTLE GIRL!
不! 不要這樣對我的女兒!
NO! SHE CAN'T-
不! 她不能
IS THERE ANYONE WE CAN CALL?
還有其他人我們可以打電話告知么?
A SPOUSE, ANOTHER FAMILY MEMBER?
您丈夫 或者其他家庭成員?
NO, IT'S JUST ME AND DIANA.
沒有 只有我和Diana
I'M SORRY.
對不起
NO...
不...
NO, LET'S GO.
不 我們走
MOM, SHE DOESN'T HAVE ANYONE!
媽媽 她沒有其他人可以依靠!
WE'RE PROBABLY JUST MAKING IT WORSE.
我們只會把事情搞得更糟
COME ON, WE DON'T BELONG HERE.
走吧 我們不該在這兒
IS DIANA HERE?
Diana在這兒么?
YEAH.
是的
SHE'S WITH HER MOM.
她呆在她媽媽身邊
I THINK SHE WANTED TO SAY GOODBYE BEFORE MOVING ON.
我想她打算在離開前說再見
OR MAYBE NOT.
或者并非如此
本字幕仅供学习交流  严禁用于商业用途
本字幕僅供學習交流  嚴禁用于商業用途
-==破烂熊字幕组==- 翻译: 校对: 时间轴:小苏
-==破爛熊字幕組==- 翻譯:滾來滾去的猴 校對:蠍蠍 時間軸:小蘇
-==http://www.RagBear.com==- Ghost Whisperer   S04E05
-==http://www.RagBear.com==- 鬼語者  第四季第5集
IT'S CRAZY.
真瘋狂
IT JUST MAKES NO SENSE. I KNOW.
- 這毫無意義 - 我知道
16 YEARS OLD, WAY TOO YOUNG.
16歲 還很年輕
IS ELI TALKING TO THE KIDS?
Eli在跟孩子談話?
YEAH, NED SAYS HE'S HELPING A LOT.
是的 Ned說他幫了個大忙
AND THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR SUGGESTING HIM FOR THAT.
謝謝你給他的建議
HE'S A GOOD THERAPIST. HE REALLY LISTENS.
他是位很好的治療師 認真聆聽
WELL, WHEN YOU TOLD ME HOW IMPORTANT DIANA AND HER MOM WERE TO EVERYONE-
嗯 當你告訴我Diana和她母親對大家有多重要時
OOH, LET ME GIVE YOU A HAND.
噢 我來幫你
YEAH, ALL THE KIDS IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD
是的 這個街區的所有小孩
USED TO GO OVER THERE AND PLAY.
都曾經去那玩
THEY JUST HAD ONE OF THOSE HOMES, YOU KNOW,
她家 你知道
VERY WARM AND INVITING. EVERYONE LOVED THEM.
很溫暖 大門永遠為你打開著 每個人都愛她們
EXCEPT FOR OLIVIA'S MOM, FROM WHAT I SAW.
除了Olivia的媽媽 從我所見推斷
I JUST DON'T GET THAT.
我真不明白
WELL, IT SEEMED MUTUAL.
呃 這應該是雙方的
YOU KNOW, MAYBE IT'S JUST BECAUSE
你知道 也許只是因為
CYNTHIA WAS WORRIED ABOUT HER DAUGHTER.
Cynthia擔心她女兒
NO, IT SEEMED LIKE SOMETHING MORE THAN THAT.
不 看上去不止是那樣
I MEAN, NED SAID THAT THE DAUGHTER WAS CHILLY WITH OLIVIA AT THE COURT.
我是指 Ned說Diana在球場上對Olivia冷若冰霜
SHE MIGHT HAVE JUST BEEN FEELING SICK, YOU KNOW?
可能她覺得身體不適 你說呢?
YEAH, MAYBE, BUT IT DIDN'T END THERE.
是的 有可能 但是事情并沒有到此為止
MEANING?
什么意思?
WHAT? WAS THERE A GHOST?
什么? 那兒有個鬼魂?
DID YOU SEE DIANA?
你看到了Diana?
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANT TO KNOW THAT?
你確定你想知道?
ANYTHING'S BETTER THAN THINKING A SPIRIT THAT YOUNG
總比想到這么年輕的靈魂
WOULD JUST VANISH!
會就此消失要好!
HI.
嗨
SHE DIDN'T VANISH. I SAW HER AT THE HOSPITAL.
她沒有消失 我在醫院看到了她
WELL, DID SHE SAY ANYTHING?
那么 她說什么了嗎?
I MEAN, DID SHE GO INTO THE LIGHT OR WHATEVER?
我是說 她現身或者做了其他什么嗎?
IMPRESSIVE! NO, SHE WENT IN A DIFFERENT DIRECTION.
想法不錯!不 她去了另一個方向
SHE FOLLOWED OLIVIA AND HER MOM HOME.
她跟著Oliva和她媽媽回家了
WELL, WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
那么 這表示什么?
MMM, MY EXPERIENCE?
嗯 根據我的經驗么?
NOTHING GOOD.
并非好事
WHAT CAN I SAY?
我能說些什么?
MOM, DAD, ARE YOU BACK?
媽媽 爸爸 你們回來了嗎?
HELLO?
有人么?
IS SOMEONE HERE?
有人在這兒么?
HELLO?!
有人嗎?!
HELLO? MR. OR MRS. KELLER, PLEASE.
喂?
CAN I SPEAK TO MR. OR MRS. KELLER? HELLO?
我可以跟Keller先生或太太說話嗎?
NO, THEY'RE NOT IN RIGHT NOW.
不 他們現在不在
CAN I TAKE A MESSAGE?
需要我幫您帶個話嗎?
I CAN'T HEAR YOU! WHO'S CALLING?
我聽不到你說話!你哪位?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
這是怎么了?!
IF THERE'S ANYTHING WE COULD DO, MRS. MORRISON...
如果我們有什么可以幫您的 Morrison太太...
JUST DON'T BE STRANGERS.
別這么陌生
MY HOME WILL ALWAYS BE OPEN TO YOU KIDS.
我家的門永遠對您的孩子敞開
TECHNO SPOOK BY THE COMPUTER.
電腦自己播放電子音樂
SCARY.
真可怕
WHERE DID YOU HEAR THAT?
你從哪聽到的?
OLIVIA WAS TELLING SOME OF HER GIRLFRIENDS
Olivia早上聚會的時候
THIS MORNING AT ASSEMBLY.
跟她的女朋友在談論
I'M REALLY SORRY, MRS. MORRISON.
我很抱歉 Morrison太太
IS THAT OLIVIA WITH DIANA'S MOM?
Olivia和Diana的媽媽在一起?
YEAH.
是的
WOW.
哇嗚
WELL, THAT DIDN'T SEEM TO GO VERY WELL.
看上去不太順利
LET'S GO SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
我們過去看看
OLIVIA?
Olivia?
HI.
嗨
MY NAME IS ELI JAMES.
我是Eli James
I'M A THERAPIST OVER AT ROCKLAND U.
Rockland U的治療師
I WAS ASKED TO COME HERE TODAY
今天我到這里
TO SPEAK TO YOUR FELLOW SCHOOLMATES ABOUT YOUR LOSS.
是來跟你的同伴們談談你們逝去的朋友
YEAH, I'VE SEEN YOU AROUND.
是的 我剛才看到你了
NED SAID, UH, YOU TWO WERE THERE WHEN IT HAPPENED?
Ned說 呃 你們兩個在事發現場?
YEAH, WHATEVER IT WAS.
嗯 的確如此
DOES ANYONE KNOW HOW SHE GOT SICK LIKE THAT?
有人知道她是怎么生病變成那樣的么?
I HAVEN'T HEARD ANYTHING YET.
我尚未聽到什么
Ned: WHEN'S THAT PICTURE FROM?
這張照片是什么時候拍的?
IT'S YOU AND DIANA, RIGHT?
照片上是你和Diana對吧?
YEAH, WE WERE, LIKE, 7 OR 8.
是的 那時我們 大概 7 8歲的樣子
SEE THAT CAST ON HER LEG?
看到她腳上的模具了么?
SHE JUST HAD HER ANKLE SURGERY,
她那時腳踝剛動過手朮
AND I SIGNED HER CAST RIGHT THERE, "OK."
我在她的模具上寫了"OK"
MY IRONIC INITIALS.
其實是我的姓名縮寫
YOU SAID YOU AND DIANA USED TO BE FRIENDS?
你是說你和Diana曾經是朋友?
YEAH, THE FIRST TIME I LIVED IN GRANDVIEW.
是的 當我剛搬到Grandview的時候
IT'S ANCIENT HISTORY.
几百年前的事情了
OLIVIA, I DO THIS A LOT,
Olivia 我遇到過很多這種事情
AND I PROMISE YOU,
我向你保証
IF YOU'RE FEELING BAD ABOUT SOMETHING,
如果你對某件事情耿耿于懷
TALKING ABOUT IT ALWAYS MAKES IT BETTER.
把它說出來反而會好過很多
WHEN WE WERE LITTLE, OUR MOMS WERE SUCH GOOD FRIENDS
在我們還小時 我們的媽媽是要好的朋友
THAT WE DID EVERYTHING TOGETHER.
因此我們也形影不離
IT WAS ALMOST LIKE WE WERE SISTERS.
我們甚至親如姐妹
WITH PLAY DATES AND SPORTS AND CAMPING.
一起玩耍 運動 露營
WE EVEN HAVE THE SAME BIRTHDAY,
我們連生日都在同一天
SO OUR PARTIES WERE LIKE THIS WHOLE BIG DEAL EVERY YEAR.
因此我們的生日派對總是每年的重頭戲
AND WHAT HAPPENED?
然后呢?
IT JUST ENDED.
就到此結束了
I REMEMBER ONE NIGHT I WOKE UP,
我記得有天夜里我醒來
AND MY MOM WAS IN BED WITH ME, AND SHE WAS ROCKING ME,
我媽媽和我一起躺在床上 她一直搖晃我
JUST CRYING AND CRYING.
哭個不停
I ASKED HER WHAT WAS WRONG,
我問她怎么了
BUT ALL SHE WOULD SAY WAS THAT SHE LOVED ME.
但是她只說她愛我
AND THEN AFTER THAT, EVERYTHING CHANGED.
從那以后 一切都變了
DIANA'S MOM AND DAD SPLIT UP,
Diana的爸爸媽媽離婚了
WE STOPPED HANGING OUT WITH THEM,
我們不再和他們一起玩
AND THEN WE GOT TRANSFERRED TO TEXAS.
之后我們搬到德克薩斯州
OR MY DAD, SO WE LEFT.
因為我爸爸調動 所以我們離開了
DID YOU AND DIANA KEEP IN TOUCH?
你和Diana有聯系過么?
WE TRIED, OR AT LEAST I DID.
我們試著 或者說我試著保持聯系
I WROTE HER AND STUFF, BUT SHE NEVER WROTE ME BACK.
我給她寫信以及寄東西 但是她從不回信
I GUESS DIANA MADE NEW FRIENDS.
我想她交了新朋友
MY MOM SAID THAT I SHOULD, TOO.
我媽媽說我也應該如此
SHE TOLD ME TO FORGET ABOUT HER.
她讓我忘記Diana
IT WAS REALLY WEIRD.
很怪異
IT WAS LIKE SHE WAS MAD AT HER, TOO.
好像她對Diana很生氣
WELL, WHAT HAPPENED WHEN YOUR DAD GOT TRANSFERRED BACK?
那么 當你爸爸調回這里時發生了什么呢?
SHE DIDN'T WRITE ME IN 8 YEARS.
她8年沒有給我寫信
I MEAN, WHY WOULD SHE WANT TO BE MY FRIEND NOW?
我是說 她怎么還可能想要再和我做朋友呢?
SHE DIDN'T NEED ME WHEN SHE HAD ALL OF THIS.
她擁有這些 她不再需要我
WHAT'S DAD DOING HERE? THANKS FOR COMING, KEVIN.
- 爸爸在這干嘛? - Kevin 謝謝你能來
EXCUSE ME, I BETTER GO.
對不起 我得走了
WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
這都怎么回事?
IF IT LOOKS LIKE A DUCK,
如果它看上去像只鴨子
QUACKS LIKE A DUCK...
像鴨子那樣呱呱叫...
Melinda: GET YOUR MIND OUT OF THE GUTTER.
把你的思想調整好
SHE PULLED HIM ASIDE, SHE HUGGED HIM,
她把他拉到一邊 她抱了他
SHE WHISPERED SWEET NOTHINGS...
她低語甜蜜的情話...
IT WAS A PRAYER VIGIL. WHO DIDN'T SHE HUG?
這是個祈禱守夜 她抱每一個人
FORGET MY MASTERS IN CLINICAL PSYCH FOR A MINUTE,
暫時把我主修臨床心理學這件事放一邊
WHICH I'D LIKE TO FORGET 'CAUSE I'M STILL PAYING OFF THE LOANS,
我也很想忘記這件事因為我還在償還貸款
AND LET'S JUST LOOK AT THE CIRCUMSTANTIAL EVIDENCE.
我們只看這些間接証據
WHAT EVIDENCE?
什么証據?
TWO WOMEN WHO USED TO BE BEST FRIENDS
兩個曾經是密友的女人
SUDDENLY BECOME ENEMIES
忽然反目成仇
AND DON'T GIVE THEIR KIDS A REASON.
并且不對孩子作解釋
YEAH, BUT THAT STILL DOESN'T EXPLAIN THE GHOST'S WEIRD BEHAVIOR
是的 但是這仍然不能解釋鬼魂在醫院的
AT THE HOSPITAL,
奇怪行為
OR FOLLOWING THE WRONG FAMILY HOME.
跟著回了別人的家
MAYBE DIANA KNEW ABOUT THE AFFAIR BEFORE SHE DIED.
也許Diana在死前知道了這件事
MAYBE THAT'S WHY SHE WAS SO NASTY TO OLIVIA
可能那就是她在網球場對Olivia
AT THE TENNIS COURTS, AND THEN WENT TO HER HOUSE TO HAUNT HER.
冷淡的原因 然后去她家恐嚇她
UNLESS...
除非...
UNLESS?
除非?
DIANA FOUND SOMETHING OUT AT THE HOSPITAL THAT PROVED MORE THAN THE AFFAIR.
Diana在醫院發現了一些東西 可以証實不止這件事
WHAT IF SHE FOUND OUT SOMETHING THAT PROVED EVERYTHING?
如果說她發現的東西可以解釋一切呢?
I'M GONNA HAVE TO BUY A VOWEL.
我得去買個原因
OK, WHAT IF OLIVIA'S DAD WAS HER DAD, TOO,
好吧 如果說Olivia的爸爸也同樣是她的爸爸
AND SHE FOUND THAT OUT IN THE HOSPITAL RECORDS?
并且她在醫院的記錄中發現了這一點?
WELL, THAT WOULD EXPLAIN WHY HE WAS AT THE VIGIL.
那么 這就能解釋他為什么在守夜上出現了
I MEAN, IF HE LOST A DAUGHTER, TOO...
我是說 如果他也失去了一個女兒...
YEAH, AND WHY DIANA WENT HOME WITH THE KELLERS
是的 并且解釋了為什么Diana跟著Keller家的人走了
INSTEAD OF HER OWN MOM.
而不是自己的媽媽
OLIVIA COULD BE THE HALF-SISTER
Olivia是她同父異母的姐妹
SHE NEVER KNEW SHE HAD. OR WANTED.
她不知道她有 或者說要這個姐妹
MAKING OLIVIA'S DAD...
使得Olivia的爸爸...
THE MAN WHO RUINED EVERYTHING.
這個毀了一切的男人
HEY, KIDDO.
嘿 小朋友
OH, GOD, YOU STARTLED ME.
哦 天啊 你嚇到我了
WHAT ARE YOU DOING UP?
你在干嘛呢?
I CAN'T SLEEP AGAIN.
我睡不著
THINKING ABOUT DIANA?
在想Diana?
UM, MOM WON'T EVEN TALK TO ME ABOUT HER.
嗯 媽媽甚至不肯跟我談她
I KNOW THAT WE WEREN'T FRIENDS AT THE END, BUT SHE DIED.
我知道最后我們不再是朋友 但是她死了
WHAT HAPPENED, DAD?
發生過什么 爸爸?
I MEAN, WITH MOM AND MRS. M.
我是說 媽媽和Morrison太太之間
HOW CAN MOM BE SO COLD TO HER, ESPECIALLY NOW?
媽媽怎么可以對她如此冷酷? 尤其是現在這種時候
IF YOU KNOW, PLEASE TELL ME.
如果你知道 拜托告訴我
HONEY, I JUST THINK THAT...
親愛的 我在想...
I DON'T KNOW, MAYBE THERE'S A LITTLE GUILT, 'CAUSE...
我不知道 也許有點內疚 因為...
WE STILL HAVE YOU.
我們仍然擁有你
DID YOU HEAR THAT?
你聽到了嗎?
IT'S THE SAME NOISE THAT I HEARD THE OTHER NIGHT.
跟那天晚上我聽到的聲音一樣
IT'S COMING FROM UPSTAIRS. IT'S THE ATTIC.
從樓上傳來的 閣樓那里
WAIT HERE, OK?
在這兒等 好嗎?
NO WAY.
不可能
DAD, I'M SCARED.
爸爸 我好怕
DON'T WORRY, HONEY. IT'S PROBABLY JUST RATS IN THE RAT TRAPS.
別怕 親愛的 很可能是捕鼠器里面的老鼠在作祟
THOSE ARE NO RATS.
那沒老鼠
THAT'S STRANGE.
這真詭異
DAD! HONEY, ARE YOU OK?
- 爸爸! - 親愛的 你還好嗎?
YEAH!
沒事!
IT'S DIANA, I KNOW IT IS.
是Diana 我知道是她
MY DAD CLAIMS THAT THERE'S SOME SORT OF REASONABLE EXPLANATION,
我爸爸堅持能找出某個合理的解釋
ALTHOUGH HE SURE ISN'T COMING UP WITH ONE.
雖然他現在一個都沒找到
SO WHAT IS HE SAYING?
那么他說了什么?
NOT TO TELL MY MOTHER.
對我媽媽守口如瓶
HE SAYS THAT HE DOESN'T WANT TO WORRY HER.
他說他不想讓她擔心
BUT HE WENT TO WORK, AND MY MOM'S OUT,
但是他去上班 我媽媽出門了
AND I'M SO SCARED. SHE KEEPS DOING IT!
我真的很怕 她一直做這種事!
I PUT THEM AWAY SO MANY TIMES,
我一次次把它們放好
AND SHE KEEPS BRINGING THEM BACK OUT.
她總是把它們拿出來
DIANA DID THIS.
Diana做的
YOU BELIEVE ME?
你相信我?
YES.
是的
WE BOTH DO.
我們都相信你
WHY?
為什么?
BECAUSE I CAN SEE SPIRITS.
因為我能看到靈魂
I'VE SEEN DIANA'S.
我見過Diana的靈魂
I WATCHED HER FOLLOW YOU HOME FROM THE HOSPITAL.
我看到她從醫院跟著你回家
THAT'S WHY NED WANTED YOU TO MEET WITH ME.
這也是為什么Ned希望你跟我見個面
DO THE PHOTOS ALWAYS LOOK LIKE THIS?
照片總是這樣排列么?
YEAH, EACH TIME I FOUND THEM THE SAME WAY.
是的 我每次看到都是這樣
STARTING WITH PHOTOS OF MY MOM AND DAD GROWING UP,
從我父母成長的照片開始
THEIR WEDDING, AND ALL OF MY BABY PHOTOS UP THROUGH NOW.
他們的婚禮 還有我幼時到現在的照片
IT'S LIKE THE WHOLE FAMILY HISTORY LAID OUT IN PHOTOS.
像整個家族史的照片展
AND THEN THERE'S THE PHONE CALLS.
還有打過來的電話
PHONE CALLS? YEAH, IT RINGS,
- 電話? - 是的 電話響
I ANSWER, AND I CAN HEAR SOMEONE TRYING TO SAY SOMETHING.
我接起 我聽到有人想要說些什么
DOES IT SOUND LIKE DIANA'S VOICE?
聽上去像Diana的聲音么?
NO, IT SOUNDED LIKE A WOMAN, BUT IT'S TOTALLY GARBLED.
不 像某個女人的聲音呢 但是很嘈雜
AND THEN IT'S CUT OFF BY THIS AWFUL SCREECHING SOUND.
然后它被這個該死的尖叫聲切斷了
UM, WHERE'S YOUR TELEPHONE?
嗯 電話機在哪?
IT'S IN THE KITCHEN.
廚房
PLEASE TELL ME YOU HAVE CALLER I.D.
請告訴我呼叫者的名字
OK, SO YOU SAID THAT THE LAST INTERRUPTED CALL CAME IN...
好的 你說上次被打斷的電話是在...
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO.
大概一個小時之前
GOT IT.
明白
NO! IT'S HAPPENING AGAIN.
不! 又來了
IT'S OK. WE'RE HERE.
沒關系 我們都在這
SHE'S GONE.
她走了
WHY DOES DIANA CARE ABOUT ME AND MY FAMILY?
為什么Diana對我和我的家人如此在意?
I DON'T KNOW.
我不知道
BUT I THINK I KNOW SOMEONE WHO DOES.
但我想有人知道
DR. TRAVIS, YOU HAVE A VISITOR
Travis醫生 您有一位訪客
IN THE MAIN LOBBY.
正在大廳等候
HI. I'M LOOKING FOR A NURSE, BUT I DON'T KNOW HER NAME.
嗨 我在找一名護士 但是我并不知道她的名字
SHE WAS WORKING THE E.R. WHEN THAT HIGH SCHOOL KID DIED,
那個高中生死時 她在急症室工作
DIANA MORRISON.
Diana Morrison
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
有什么我能幫你的么?
WELL, IT WAS JUST A TOUGH DAY,
呃 那是痛苦不堪的一天
AND SO I WANTED TO THANK HER FOR REACHING OUT TO THE FAMILY.
我想謝謝她為那個家人做的事
HER NAME IS PERRY, DOROTHY PERRY.
她叫Perry Dorothy Perry
I'M SURE SHE'D APPRECIATE IT, IF SHE WERE HERE,
我想如果她在這兒定會對你非常感激
I KNOW SHE WAS TRYING TO MAKE SOME COPIES,
我知道她正在復印一些東西
AND A PHONE CALL, AND...
以及打個電話...
NOTHING WAS WORKING FOR HER.
這兩件事都不太順利
IS THERE A COPIER NEARBY?
附近有復印機么?
UM, THE RECORDS ROOM ON THE THIRD FLOOR.
嗯 在三樓的記錄室
GREAT. THANK YOU.
太好了 謝謝
HELLO? ANYBODY THERE?
哈羅 有人在嗎
HEY!
嘿!
WAIT, NURSE PERRY!
等等 Perry護士!
NURSE PERRY! NO, I CAN'T!
Perry護士!
I JUST WANT TO TALK!
我只是想跟你談談!
OH, MY GOD! PLEASE, SOMEBODY, HELP ME!
哦天啊! 來人啊 幫幫我!
HELP!
救命!
HEY.
嘿
THE WORD IS, SHE'S GOING TO BE OUT FOR A WHILE.
他們說她得睡上一段時間
THEY'VE GOT HER ON HEAVY PAINKILLERS
他們給她打了很重的止疼藥
AND ANTI-ANXIETY MEDS.
和抗焦慮藥
DID YOU GET ANYTHING ELSE?
你還知道什么?
OH, YEAH. SHE GOT WORKED OVER PRETTY GOOD.
哦 是的 她傷的很重
HEAD LACERATION, 2 BROKEN RIBS,
頭部裂傷 斷了兩根肋骨
HAIRLINE FRACTURE OF HER COLLARBONE.
鎖骨骨裂
DIANA WAS SO ANGRY AT HER.
Diana對她恨之入骨
YEAH, MEL, HOW WAS AN E.R. NURSE INVOLVED IN THIS?
是的 Mel 為什么急症室的護士也會牽涉其中?
I THINK SHE WAS ON THE PHONE WITH OLIVIA'S FAMILY
我想她打電話給Olivia的家人
TRYING TO TELL THEM SOMETHING.
要告訴他們一些事情
WHEN I SAW HER, SHE WAS COMING OUT OF THE RECORD ROOM.
我看到她時 她正從記錄室沖出來
MELINDA, COME ON, IT'S ONE THING TO GO ASKING AROUND
Melinda 求你了 查病歷
ABOUT A MEDICAL CONDITION, IT'S ANOTHER TO-
是一回事 去...
YEAH, BUT WE STILL DON'T KNOW WHAT CAUSED DIANA'S DEATH!
是的 可是我們還是不知道Diana為什么會死!
I DON'T THINK THE ANSWER IS IN THOSE RECORDS. THOSE ARE OLD RECORDS.
我不認為答案會那些記錄里 那都是些舊的記錄
MAYBE IT WAS SOMETHING ELSE.
也許是另外一些事情
MAYBE SOMETHING IN DIANA'S PAST
也許是在Diana的過去
THAT THE DOCTOR SHOULD HAVE SEEN.
醫生應該看到卻沒有看到的一些事
MAYBE THEY MADE A MISTAKE.
可能他們犯了個錯誤
I MEAN, SHE WAS A HEALTHY 16-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
我是說 她是一個健康的16歲女孩
OK, THEN IF THAT'S THE CASE,
好吧 如果是你說的情況
WHY IS THE GHOST HAUNTING OLIVIA AND HER FAMILY?
為什么她的靈魂要對Olivia和她的家人作祟?
I DON'T KNOW.
我不知道
THE GIRL IS DEAD, A WOMAN IS HURT,
一個女孩子死了 一個女人受了重傷
AND I AM OUT OF THEORIES.
我只是在推測
PLEASE.
求你了
ALL I NEED IS 10 MINUTES.
我只要十分鐘
HERE'S M.
這里是M開頭的
MOORE, MORIARTY. WHERE'S MORRISON?
Moore Moriarty Morrison在哪?
MISSING. HOLD ON A SECOND.
不見了 等一下
THESE MUST BE WAITING TO BE RE-FILED.
這些肯定是打算重新歸檔的
THERE YOU GO.
找到了
HER MEDICAL RECORDS.
她的病歷
THESE ARE FROM LIKE 8 YEARS AGO.
這些大概是8年前的
OH, LOOKS LIKE SHE HAD AN OPERATION.
哦 看上去她做過一個手朮
FRACTURED HER ANKLE.
踝關節骨折
AND DIANA'S BIRTH RECORD.
還有Diana的出生記錄
MR. KELLER'S NOT LISTED AS HER FATHER.
沒有列出Keller先生是她的父親
WHY WOULD A NURSE WANT COPIES OF THIS STUFF?
為什么一個護士要復印這個東西?
WAIT A MINUTE, THIS IS WEIRD. LOOK AT THIS.
等等 太奇怪了 看這個
HER BLOOD TYPE ON HER SURGERY RECORD
她手朮記錄上的血型跟
DOESN'T MATCH HER BLOOD TYPE ON HER BIRTH RECORD.
出生記錄上的有出入
A.B., O.
A.B.  O.
DO HOSPITALS MAKE MISTAKES LIKE THAT?
醫院會犯這種錯誤嗎?
IT'S POSSIBLE, BUT RARE.
有可能 但很少
OR MAYBE THERE'S ANOTHER POSSIBILITY.
也許有另外一種可能性
????
我看了她放在一起的記錄
I KNOW WHY YOU'RE ANGRY,
知道你為什么憤怒
BUT I THINK SHE WAS TRYING TO DO THE RIGHT THING.
但我認為她在努力做正確的事
SHE WANTED THE TRUTH TO COME OUT.
她想要真相水落石出
THERE ARE SOME MISTAKES THAT YOU CAN'T FIX!
總有些破洞是你沒辦法修補的!
I FOUND THAT OUT THE DAY THAT I DIED.
在我死的那天我就發現了
ANSWER ME!
回答我!
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?!
到底發生了什么?!
I FOLLOWED HER TO THE RECORDS ROOM.
我跟著她進了記錄室
AND RIGHT AWAY, I SAW SOMETHING WEIRD.
然后我立刻發現了一些奇怪的事情
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
你在找什么?
AND THAT'S WHEN I REALIZED WHAT HAPPENED.
然后我意識到發生了什么
OLIVIA AND I WERE SWITCHED AT BIRTH.
Olivia和我在出生時被交換了
THE BLOOD TYPES DIDN'T MATCH, I KNOW.
血型不匹配 我知道
BUT THAT'S NOT WHAT WAS REALLY UPSETTING HER.
但是這不是真正讓她忐忑不安的
SHE LOOKED SO GUILTY!
她顯得如此內疚!
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
我做了些什么?
LIKE SHE HAD DONE SOMETHING AWFUL.
好像她做了可怕的事
YOU WERE THERE THE DAY I WAS BORN, TOO?
我出生那天你也在嗎?
AND THAT'S WHEN IT HIT ME-
然后我被這個事情打擊到了-
IT WAS HER MISTAKE.
是她犯的錯
THAT'S HOW SHE KNEW TO LOOK IN THOSE FILES.
這就是為什么她知道要看這些文件
IT'S HER FAULT!
是她的錯!
LOOK, I KNOW THAT YOU'RE UPSET,
看 我知道你很生氣
BUT I...
但是...
I THINK IT WAS JUST A MISTAKE, YOU KNOW?
我想這只是一個失誤 你說呢?
A STUPID ACCIDENT.
一樁愚蠢的事故
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S STUPID?
你知道什么才是愚蠢么?
HOW COULD I NOT HAVE KNOWN?!
我居然從未發現過?!
I MEAN, WE EVEN HAVE THE SAME BIRTHDAY!
我的意思是 我們甚至是同天生日!
AND MY-SO CALLED FAMILY?
還有我那個所謂的家庭?
MY MOM IS BLONDE, BLUE-EYED,
我媽媽金發碧眼
A SEMI-PRO TENNIS PLAYER.
是個半職業網球運動員
SO I ALWAYS TOLD MYSELF THAT I SUCKED AT TENNIS
所以我經常安慰自己我對網球一竅不通
BECAUSE I TOOK AFTER MY DAD.
是因為我像我爸爸的緣故
WELL, IT TURNS OUT,
結果呢
I DO TAKE AFTER MY MOM,
我的確跟我媽媽很像
I JUST HAD THE WRONG ONE.
只不過像的是另外一個
LOOK, I KNOW THAT THIS IS PAINFUL, BUT I CAN HELP YOU,
看 我知道這很痛苦 但我可以幫你
TALK TO YOUR MOM, YOUR BIRTH FAMILY.
跟你媽媽談談 你的親生父母
NO! THEY CAN'T KNOW.
不! 他們不能知道
WELL, I THINK YOU NEED THEM TO.
我想你得讓他們知道
THAT'S WHY YOU WENT TO THE KELLER'S HOUSE, RIGHT?
這也是為什么你去Keller家的原因 對嗎?
SO THAT YOU COULD RECONNECT WITH THE FAMILY YOU CAME FROM?
這樣你就能重新投入親生的家人的懷抱?
YOU NEED TO MAKE PEACE WITH THIS SO THAT YOU CAN MOVE ON.
你必須接受這一點你才可以繼續往前走
THAT WOMAN'S MISTAKE HAS CAUSED ENOUGH DAMAGE ALREADY.
那個女人的錯誤已經造成了足夠大的傷害
WELL, YOU DON'T CONTROL THAT ANYMORE.
可是你控制不了這個后果
I KNOW THAT'S UPSETTING, BUT-
我知道這很痛苦 但是-
TAKE A LOOK AT THAT NURSE
看看那個護士
AND TELL ME WHAT I CAN AND I CAN'T DO.
再告訴我什么能做什么不能做
I WILL DO WHATEVER I HAVE TO DO.
我會做所有我必須做的
NO ONE CAN FIND OUT.
沒人會找到答案
HI, MS. PERRY.
嗨 Perry女士
UM, MY NAME IS MELINDA GORDON
呃 我的名字是Melinda Grodon
AND I'D LIKE TO TALK TO YOU,
我想跟您談談
IF YOU'RE FEELING UP TO IT.
如果您覺得可以的話
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO CAME LOOKING FOR ME WHEN I FELL?
你是我摔下樓梯時來找我的那位?
YES.
是的
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT HAVE SOME INFORMATION ON DIANA MORRISON,
我想也許您對Diana Morrison知道些什么
AND NOW I COULDN'T BE MORE CERTAIN THAT YOU DO.
而現在我對這點十分確信
I KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
我知道Diana
THE DAY THAT DIANA WAS BORN.
出生那天的事
I KNOW THAT SHE WAS SWITCHED WITH OLIVIA KELLER.
她跟Olivia Keller交換了
LOOK, I KNOW THAT YOU'RE SCARED.
看 我知道您很害怕
A LOT OF REALLY STRANGE THINGS ARE HAPPENING TO YOU,
您身上發生了很多匪夷所思的事情
BUT TRUST ME-
但相信我-
THEY WON'T END UNTIL YOU ADMIT WHAT YOU DID.
除非您承認您的所作所為 否則它們不會就此終止
WHAT I DID?
我做了什么?
NO! I-
不! 我-
I WAS THERE WHEN IT HAPPENED,
我當時的確在場
BUT I'M NOT THE ONE WHO SWITCHED THOSE GIRLS.
但我不是誤換了兩個孩子的人
OK, THE DAY THAT DIANA MORRISON WAS BORN,
好吧 Diana Morrison出生那天
THERE'D BEEN THIS HUGE ACCIDENT ON THE INTERSTATE.
洲際公路發生了一場大車禍
WE WERE UNDERSTAFFED AND OVERWHELMED.
我們人手不足 手忙腳亂
THE BRACELET MUST HAVE COME OFF IN THE BATH.
手環肯定是在給寶寶洗澡時脫落了
THE CHARGE NURSE SEEMS CONFUSED.
負責的護士看上去有點困惑
UM, IS EVERYTHING OK?
呃 這還好吧?
YOU WERE SENT TO ROOM 214.
你被派去了214房
YOU GOT TO GET MRS. KELLER UP AND WALKING. GO, NOW!
你去把Keller太太扶起來走走 現在 快去!
I WAS FRESH OUT OF NURSING SCHOOL.
我那時剛從護士學校畢業
I WAS TRYING TO LEARN WITHOUT ASKING TOO MANY QUESTIONS.
我努力學習 盡量不問太多問題
WHAT COULD I DO?
我能做什么?
I DIDN'T HAVE ANY PROOF.
我沒有任何証據
IT WAS JUST A FEELING.
只有直覺
BUT I DID REMEMBER THOSE GIRLS' NAMES.
但我記住了這兩個孩子的名字
THEN I SAW THE MOTHERS BONDING
我看到兩個母親黏在一起
AND TALKING IN THE HALLWAYS,
在走廊交談
AND...
以及...
CRADLING THEIR BABIES.
搖著搖籃里的寶寶
AND THEN YOU SAW THEM AGAIN 16 YEARS LATER.
然后16年后你再次遇到了她們
I RECOGNIZED HER NAME WHEN THE PARAMEDICS BROUGHT HER IN.
護理人員把她帶進來時我記起了她的名字
DO WE HAVE HER NAME?
知道她名字嗎?
DIANA MORRISON.
Diana Morrison
CIRCUMSTANCES OF HER DEATH,
她的死亡情況
THE BLOOD CLOT,
血液凝結
IT MADE ME WONDER ALL OVER AGAIN.
讓我再度產生懷疑
SO I PULLED THE GIRL'S MEDICAL RECORDS.
所以我找出她的病史
THAT'S WHAT CONFIRMED IT.
結果証實了我的猜想
YOU KNOW, I'VE BEEN TRYING TO CONTACT THE FAMILIES EVER SINCE.
你知道 我一直在努力聯系兩個家庭
IT'S JUST THAT SOME...
只是有些...
SOMETHING JUST... DOESN'T WANT TO LET...
有些東西...不想讓我...
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO ME?
我身上發生了什么?
LOOK, IT'S GONNA BE OK.
一切都會好起來了
YOU SUSPECTED FOR 16 YEARS.
你懷疑了16年
I NEED TO KNOW WHY YOU'RE SO DETERMINED TO TELL THEM NOW.
我想知道為什么現在你這么執著的想要告訴她們
BECAUSE THE BLOOD CLOT THAT KILLED DIANA
因為Diana是血液凝結致死
WAS A GENETIC CONDITION.
是一種遺傳病
IT COULD AFFECT SOMEONE ELSE IN HER BIOLOGICAL FAMILY.
會影響她的血親家庭中的其他人
THEY HAVE TO BE TOLD.
他們必須知道這一點
THAT'S A TOUGH ONE, EVEN FOR YOU.
這是塊燙山芋啊 哪怕是對你來說
I HAVE TO TELL THEM, OBVIOUSLY.
很明顯 我必須告訴他們
I MEAN THE KELLERS NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THE DISEASE,
我的意思是Keller家必須知道這個病
AND THEN CYNTHIA MORRISON'S GOING TO FIND OUT.
然后Cynthia Morrison將找出答案
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
我只是不知道對鬼魂和兩個家庭
TO THE GHOST OR THE FAMILIES.
會發生些什么
I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE.
我無法想象
I MEAN, MOURNING YOUR CHILD,
我是說 還在追悼你的孩子
ONLY TO FIND OUT SHE ISN'T YOURS.
結果卻發現她不是你的
AND THEN THE CHILD THAT IS YOURS,
然后你的孩子
BELONGS TO SOMEONE ELSE.
卻屬于別人
OLIVIA'S PARENTS, TOO.
對Olivia的父母來說也一樣
I MEAN, THEIR BIRTH CHILD IS DEAD.
我的意思是 他們的親生孩子死了
THEY'RE NEVER GOING TO GET TO KNOW HER AS THEIRS.
他們不能像了解自己的孩子那樣去了解她了
I GUESS THAT'S WHY DIANA'S BEEN FIGHTING SO HARD
我猜這是Diana如此抗拒的原因
TO KEEP THIS ALL A SECRET.
為了保守這些秘密
IT'S ALL JUST TO PROTECT EVERYONE FROM THE BIG BOMBSHELL.
保護所有人免受這爆炸性事實的傷害
WHO DO YOU TELL FIRST?
你打算先告訴誰?
I THINK I HAVE TO START WITH THE WOMAN WHO RAISED HER.
我想我得先跟她的養母談談
SO KIND OF YOU TO BRING THIS BY.
謝謝你送這個來
I THINK EVERYONE MISSES DIANA.
我想大家都很想念Diana
I KNOW THAT NED DOES.
我知道Ned很想她
OH, HE'S A SWEET BOY.
哦 他真貼心
IS THAT HOW YOU KNOW MY DAUGHTER, THROUGH NED?
你是通過Ned認識我女兒的么?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
你在做什么?
I WARNED YOU NOT TO DO THIS!
我警告你別輕舉妄動!
ACTUALLY, I DIDN'T KNOW DIANA WHEN SHE WAS ALIVE.
事實上 Diana生前我并不認識她
HMM.
嗯
BUT I'VE TALKED TO HER RECENTLY.
但是我最近跟她交談
UM...
嗯...
I SEE EARTHBOUND SPIRITS.
我可以看到無法超度的靈魂
THAT'S HOW I KNOW THAT DIANA'S HERE.
這是我知道Diana在這兒的原因
I CAME HERE BECAUSE SHE'S NOT AT PEACE,
我來是因為她很不平靜
AND THERE'S A REASON WHY SHE CAN'T MOVE ON.
而且有件事情讓她不能超度
I DON'T UNDERSTAND. IS THIS SOME KIND OF JOKE?
我不明白 你是在開玩笑嗎?
NO, THIS IS...
不 這是...
IT'S VERY REAL.
這是千真萬確的
DIANA'S BEEN TRYING TO PROTECT YOU FROM SOMETHING,
Diana想保護你 有些東西她不希望讓你知道
BUT I THINK IT'S SOMETHING YOU SHOULD KNOW,
但是我認為你應該了解
BECAUSE IT'S GOING TO COME OUT EVENTUALLY.
因為它最終還是會浮出水面
YOU HAVE NO RIGHT TO DO THIS!
你有什么權利這么做
WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?!
你以為你是誰?!
I SPOKE TO A NURSE AT MERCY HOSPITAL,
我跟慈善醫院的一個護士交談過
DOROTHY PERRY.
Dorothy Perry
SHE WAS THERE THE DAY THAT DIANA DIED,
Diana死的那天
AND THE DAY THAT SHE WAS BORN.
和出生那天她都在場
THE SAME DAY THAT OLIVIA KELLER WAS BORN.
她和Olivia Keller同日出生
STOP IT! STOP!
住口! 住口!
WHY IS THIS SUDDENLY COMING OUT NOW?
為什么這事突然冒出來了?
WHO TOLD YOU ABOUT ALL THIS?
誰告訴你這事的?
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT?
你知道我在說什么?
MMM, I HAVE A PRETTY GOOD FEELING.
嗯 我對此有過直覺
WHAT?!
什么?!
HOW DID YOU FIND OUT?
你怎么知道的?
I SAW A BLOOD PANEL
我看到她的血液指標
FROM THE ANKLE SURGERY SHE HAD WHEN SHE WAS 8.
是她8歲時動的腳踝手朮
IS THAT WHEN YOU REALIZED THE TRUTH?
你也是這樣知道真相的嗎?
NO, IT WAS LONG BEFORE THAT.
不 比這早的多的多
I'VE KNOWN DIANA WASN'T MINE
几乎在我剛擁有她時
ALMOST AS LONG AS I'VE HAD HER.
我就知道她不是我親生的了
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
不可能
YOU NEVER SAID ANYTHING.
你從沒跟我提過
PLEASE.
請坐
I HAD A LONG LABOR,
我陣痛很長
AND SO DID LISA KELLER.
Lisa Keller也是
WE MET WALKING THE HALLS,
我們在大廳散步時遇見
PASSING THE TIME TOGETHER,
一起度過時光
WAITING FOR IT TO HAPPEN.
等待孩子出生那一刻
BOTH HAVING GIRLS, EXCITED.
都生了個女兒 興奮異常
AND WE JUST BECAME FRIENDS.
然后我們成了好友
THERE'S SO MUCH JOY.
那時總是歡聲笑語
AND THEN WHAT HAPPENED?
之后呢?
THEN I BROUGHT DIANA HOME, AND SOMETHING FELT OFF.
之后我帶Diana回家 我覺得若有所失
EVERYBODY THOUGHT IT WAS POST-PARTUM DEPRESSION,
每個人都以為是產后憂郁症
AND AT FIRST, SO DID I.
最初我也這么以為
I MEAN, I LOVE MY LITTLE GIRL.
我的意思是 我愛我的女兒
BUT THAT FEELING DIDN'T GO AWAY.
但那種感覺揮之不去
SO, WHEN DID YOU SUSPECT
那么 你什么時候懷疑
THAT DIANA WASN'T YOUR BABY?
Diana不是你親生的?
AS THEY STARTED TO GROW OLDER,
當孩子們一點點長大
I STARTED TO NOTICE SIMILARITIES
我開始覺察到
BETWEEN ME AND OLIVIA THAT I DIDN'T NOTICE
我和Olivia之間的相似處 而這些我卻沒有在我和
WITH DIANA. WHEN SHE PLAYED TENNIS,
Diana之間看到 當她打網球
SHE PLAYED LIKE ME. SHE HAD MY MOTHER'S EYES.
動作和我如出一轍 她的眼睛和我母親的一模一樣
AND SOMETIMES, WHEN I LOOKED AT HER AND SHE SMILED,
有時 我看著她而她沖著我笑
I FELT LIKE I WAS LOOKING AT A MIRROR.
我會誤以為我是在照鏡子
WHAT ABOUT WHEN YOU LOOKED AT ME?
那當你看著我的時候呢?
DID YOU CONTACT LISA KELLER?
你什么時候聯系Lisa Keller的?
NOT UNTIL THE PRE-SURGERY BLOOD WORK CONFIRMED IT.
直到手朮前的血檢確定了這一點
THAT'S WHEN I CALLED LISA.
于是我打電話給Lisa
HOW DID SHE REACT?
她是什么反應?
SHE DIDN'T BELIEVE IT.
她不相信
REFUSED TO HAVE OLIVIA TESTED.
拒絕讓Olivia進行測試
SHE CUT OFF ALL CONTACT.
她切斷了我們間的所有聯系
THEY MOVED TO TEXAS.
舉家搬到德克薩斯
SHE SAID IT WAS FOR KEVIN'S JOB.
她說是因為Kevin工作調動
SHE WAS RUNNING AWAY FROM THE UNCOMFORTABLE TRUTH.
她遠遠逃離了這個尷尬的真相
SO MY OWN MOTHER DIDN'T WANT ME,
就是說我的親生母親不想要我
AND YOU COULDN'T GET RID OF ME?
而你卻無法擺脫我?
LET HER EXPLAIN. SHE ALREADY HAS.
- 聽她解釋 - 她已經說得很明白
AND IF THEY LOVED THE TWO OF US SO LITTLE,
如果她們愛我們兩個只有這種程度
THEN THEY WON'T MISS US WHEN WE'RE BOTH GONE!
那么即使我們都離開她們也不會想念我們!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
這是怎么回事?
IS, UH, DIANA-
是 呃 Diana-
WE NEED TO GO SEE OLIVIA BEFORE DIANA DOES.
我們要趕在Diana之前去見Olivia
DIANA, STOP IT!
Diana 停下!
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
你為什么這么做?
????
這算什么?!
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME, DIANA?
你想從我身上得到什么 Diana?
MRS. KELLER?
Keller太太?
YES?
怎么了?
MY NAME IS MELINDA GORDON.
我是Melinda Gordon
IS YOUR DAUGHTER HOME?
您女兒在家嗎?
WHAT IS THIS ABOUT?
這是做什么?
TRUST HER, LISA. THIS IS IMPORTANT.
相信她 Lisa 這事很重要
OH, MY GOD! WHAT HAPPENED?
哦 天啊!發生了什么?
WHO-
誰-
WHO DID ALL OF THIS? LIVVY? SWEETIE?
這些都誰干的?Livvy?親愛的?
OLIVIA?
Olivia?
HER BACKPACK IS NOT HERE.
她的背包不在這兒
OR HER CELL PHONE, CLOTHES, LAPTOP.
還有她的手機 衣服 筆記本電腦
OH, MY GOD!
哦 天哪!
WHAT DID YOU DO?!
你都干了什么?!
DID YOU TELL OLIVIA?
你告訴了Olivia?
NO.
我沒有
THEN HOW DID SHE KNOW ABOUT THESE?
那么她怎么知道這些?
HOW DID SHE KNOW TO EVEN LOOK FOR THESE?
她如何知道要找這些東西?
DIANA MUST HAVE LED HER TO THEM.
Diana指給她看的
WHAT?!
什么?!
THESE ARE ALL LETTERS FROM DIANA TO OLIVIA.
這些都是Diana寫給Olivia的信
AND SHE THOUGHT I NEVER WROTE HER BACK.
可是她卻認為我從不回信
HER MOM MUST HAVE KEPT THEM FROM HER.
一定她媽媽把這些藏好從不讓她知道
YOU KEPT THESE FROM OLIVIA?
你沒有把這些給Olivia?
MY GOD, LISA.
天啊 Lisa
ARE YOU SO SELFISH THAT YOU WOULDN'T EVEN
你真的如此自私 甚至不肯
LET OUR DAUGHTERS BE FRIENDS?
讓我們的女兒成為朋友們嗎?
DIANA'S BABY BRACELET.
Diana出生時的手環
I SENT THIS TO LISA, TRYING ONE LAST TIME
我把它寄給Lisa 是自告知她真相后
AFTER I TOLD HER THE TRUTH.
的最后一次嘗試
AND NOW OLIVIA KNOWS THE TRUTH.
現在Olivia知道真相了
I HAVE TO FIND HER, I HAVE TO CALL THE POLICE!
我要找到她 我得打電話給警察!
NO, YOU DON'T. YOU KNOW WHERE SHE IS, DON'T YOU?
不 你不必 你知道她在哪對嗎?
PLEASE.
求你了
OLIVIA NEEDS YOUR HELP.
Olivia需要你的幫助
SWEETHEART!
親愛的!
OH, I'M SO GLAD WE FOUND YOU!
哦 真慶幸我們找到了你!
STAY AWAY FROM ME.
離我遠點
I UNDERSTAND WHY YOU'RE ANGRY, BUT, OLIVIA,
我能理解你為什么生氣 可是 Olivia
YOU HAVE TO KNOW THAT-
你得明白-
WHAT? WHAT YOU KNEW FOR THE LAST 8 YEARS?
什么?你在過去8年中所知道的?
I FOUND THE LETTER.
我找到了那封信
DEAR LISA, I WANTED YOU TO HAVE SOMETHING OF YOUR DAUGHTER, DIANA.
親愛的Lisa 我想讓你知道你女兒Diana的一些事
OLIVIA...
Olivia...
DON'T TALK TO ME, I CAN'T HEAR ANY MORE LIES!
別跟我說話 我不想再聽謊話了!
OLIVIA, DON'T. DON'T TALK TO YOUR MOTHER THAT WAY.
Olivia 別這樣 別這么跟你媽媽說話
MY MOTHER? AND WHO ARE YOU?
我媽媽?那么你算誰?
THE WOMAN WHO GAVE BIRTH TO ME
生了我
LET ME PLAY IN THEIR HOUSE AND THEN LET ME GO?
讓我在她家玩然后讓我走的女人么?
AND NOT JUST SOMEBODY ELSE'S HOUSE,
而且不是把我趕去別人的家
BUT HALFWAY ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
而是把我趕到了這個國家的另一邊
WERE YOU RELIEVED WHEN WE MOVED?
我們搬走時你是不是覺得如釋重負?
DID THE TWO OF YOU WORK ALL OF THAT OUT TOGETHER?
你們倆一起想出的這個辦法嗎?
SHE TRIED.
她嘗試過
WHEN SHE FOUND OUT THE TRUTH,
當她發現事情真相
SHE TRIED TO TALK TO ME, BUT, OLIVIA,
她試著跟我溝通 可是 Olivia
YOU WERE MY DAUGHTER AND SO WAS DIANA,
你和Diana都是我的女兒
AND I COULDN'T LOSE YOU BOTH!
我不能同時失去你們倆!
BOTH, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
她們倆 你是什么意思?
WELL, FROM THE TIME THEY COULD WALK,
從她們蹣跚學步那天起
THEY WOULD FOLLOW YOU EVERYWHERE.
她們跟著你滿世界跑
PUPPET SHOWS, GAMES, SPORTS.
跟著你去看木偶戲 玩游戲 做運動
KIDS LOVE YOU.
孩子們喜歡你
WHAT IF THEY HAD TO CHOOSE?
如果她們必須做個選擇呢?
THEY WOULD BOTH CHOOSE YOU.
她們都會選你
LISA, LOOK AT YOUR DAUGHTER.
Lisa 看著你的女兒
YOUR DAUGHTER OLIVIA.
你的女兒Olivia
AS MUCH AS IT KILLS ME TO SAY THAT.
這句話讓我心如刀割
WHY DO YOU THINK SHE'S SO ANGRY?
你知道她為什么這么生氣么?
IT'S NOT BECAUSE YOU KEPT THIS FROM HER.
不是因為你沒有告訴她真相
SHE THINKS THIS MEANS THAT YOU DON'T LOVE HER,
她認為這意味著你不愛她
AND THERE'S NOTHING MORE IN THE WORLD
這世上她唯一想要的
THAT SHE WANTS THAN YOUR LOVE.
就是你的愛
WELL, I ALWAYS THOUGHT
我一直覺得
THERE WAS NOTHING MORE IN THE WORLD I WANTED THAN HERS.
在這世上我唯一想要的是她的愛
AND THEN...
然后...
YOU CALLED ME THAT DAY,
那天你打電話給我
AND I WANTED MORE.
我想得到更多
WHENEVER I LOOKED AT EITHER ONE OF THEM.
每當我看著她們倆中的一個
OLIVIA, YOU ARE MY LITTLE GIRL.
Olivia 你是我的心愛的女兒
NOTHING CAN CHANGE THAT.
沒什么能改變這一點
BUT DIANA, HER HANDS,
可是Diana 她的手
HER EYES,
眼睛
THE WAY SHE WALKED- SHE WAS MINE, TOO.
走路的方式-她也是我的孩子
I'M SORRY
我很抱歉
THAT I TORE OUR DAUGHTERS APART.
我強行分開了我們的女兒
I'M SORRY THAT I ABANDONED BOTH OF YOU.
我很抱歉拋棄了你們倆
HOW COULD YOU NOT WANT BOTH OF THEM?
你怎么可能會不想要她們?
I KNOW I DID.
我知道我想要
I DON'T WANT THEM TO HURT ANYMORE.
我不想她們再受傷害了
DIANA WANTS TO FORGIVE YOU.
Diana決定原諒你們
WAIT, DIANA'S HERE?
等下 Diana在這?
THAT'S HOW WE FOUND YOU.
所以我們才能在這找到你
SHE TOLD ME THAT YOU GUYS USED TO PLAY HERE TOGETHER.
她告訴我你們曾經在這里一起玩耍
TELL OLIVIA THAT I DID MAKE NEW FRIENDS, BUT...
告訴Olivia我的確交了新朋友 但是...
THERE WERE NONE LIKE HER.
沒人比得上她
SHE WANTS YOU TO KNOW THAT SHE MISSED YOU.
她希望你知道她想念你
THERE WAS NO ONE LIKE YOU.
你對她來說是獨一無二的
I MISSED HER, TOO.
我也想念她
I STILL DO.
現在仍是
SWEETHEART, WE'RE GOING TO SIT DOWN,
親愛的 我們會坐下來
WE'RE GOING TO TALK ALL OF THIS THROUGH.
把這件事好好的從頭到尾談一談
WE'LL FIGURE OUT WHERE TO GO FROM HERE...
我們會想出如何從這里開始...
TOGETHER.
我們一起
SHE'S SAYING GOOD-BYE.
她在說再見
OH...
噢...
WILL SHE BE OK?
她會沒事嗎?
SHE WANTS TO KNOW IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT
她想知道如果沒有她在身邊
WITHOUT HER.
你是不是可以過得很好
I'M NOT GOING TO LIE TO YOU, SWEET GIRL.
我不想對你說謊 我親愛的女兒
NOTHING IS EVER GOING TO BE THE SAME.
我的世界已經天翻地覆
REMEMBER WHAT YOU USED TO TELL ME
還記得你曾經告訴我的話嗎?
WHEN I HAD A BAD DAY
當我過了糟糕的一天
OR I DIDN'T DO WELL?
或者表現不好時
YOU WOULD ALWAYS SAY
你總是說
THAT THE ONLY THING THAT MATTERED TO YOU
你只關心一件事
IS THAT YOU KNEW I TRIED MY BEST.
就是你知道我已經盡了全力
THAT'S WHAT I NEED YOU TO DO.
這也是我希望你能做到的
I NEED YOU TO TRY TO BE OK.
我希望你試著好好生活
FOR ME.
為了我
SHE WANTS YOU TO TRY.
她希望你可以嘗試
JUST LIKE YOU USED TO TELL HER TO DO.
就象你曾經告誡過她的那樣
SHE NEEDS YOU TO PROMISE THAT YOU'LL AT LEAST TRY.
她想要你答應至少會去嘗試
I WILL, SWEET GIRL.
我會的 好孩子
I'LL TRY.
我會試著的
SHE'S GONE.
她走了
THANK YOU.
多謝你
LONG DAY?
漫長的一天?
OH...
噢...
THE LONGEST.
太漫長了
DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
想談談么?
WHEN I...
當我...
SAW THOSE TWO MOTHERS
看到那兩個母親
LOVE DAUGHTERS THAT WEREN'T EVEN REALLY THEIRS,
如此深愛甚至不是自己親生的女兒
IT JUST MADE ME REALIZE...
我忽然明白...
IF WE CAN'T DO THIS...
如果我們不能...
IF WE CAN'T HAVE A BABY, WOULD...
如果我們不能生個小寶寶...
WOULD YOU CONSIDER ADOPTION?
你會考慮領養嗎?
ABSOLUTELY.
當然了
I REALLY...
我真的...
NEEDED TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT,
需要聽你說這句話
BECAUSE THE TESTS AND THE TRYING-
因為測試和嘗試-
BUT MEL, LOOK AT THIS.
但是Mel 看看這個
ARE THESE MY RESULTS?
這些是我的結果?
WELL, I DID RUN INTO DR. CHEN TODAY.
呃 我今天遇到了陳醫生
WELL, WHAT IS THIS PRESCRIPTION?
那么 這個處方是做什么的?
IT'S FOR A HORMONE.
是為了荷爾蒙
IT HELPS THE EMBRYO ATTACH ITSELF.
幫助胚胎自己依附母體
IT BASICALLY MAKES IT FEEL MORE AT HOME
簡單地說就是讓它覺得更加安心
SO IT CAN SETTLE AND GROW.
這樣它就可以穩定下來慢慢成長
AND THIS IS ALL WE NEED?
這就是我們需要的?
YEAH.
是的
SO WE'RE GOING TO BE ABLE TO HAVE A BABY?
所以我們可以生個小寶寶了?
破烂熊字幕组 -==http://www.RagBear.com==- 欢迎加入
破爛熊字幕組 -==http://www.RagBear.com==- 歡迎加入